Luther-Bagby collection, Inclusive: 1821-2001, Bulk: 1890-1970
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Literary Productions, 1912-2001; 4; 19 document boxes and 9 folders of oversized materials.
  - General, 1912-1977; 6
    - Music: (3 of 3), undated (Box 129 OVZ, Folder 4)
    - Maps, 1965, undated (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Newsletters: William B. Harrison, 1955 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Newsletters: "The Luther Family", 1945 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Broadsides, 1938, 1945, 1951, 1963-1965 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Catalogues, 1932-1967, undated (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Posters, 1939, 1958, undated (Box 129 OVZ, Folder 5)
    - Posters: "Missionaries Supported by Our 1934 Lottie Moon Christmas Offering" (Box 129 OVZ, Folder 6)
- Photographs, circa 1850s, 1974; 5; 13 document boxes and 1 ovesized box.
  The photographs in this series are arranged by family when possible, and then by topic. The main themes throughout the photographs include schools, churches, friends and associates, and travel. There are postcards in the travel subseries. The arrangement of many of the family photographs was done using notes from donors and other family members to determine who is pictured.
  Photograph Albums; Photographic print
  - Luther: John Hill Luther and Family, circa 1867-1877; 1896, undated (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Luther: John Hill Luther and Family, circa 1880s, undated (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Luther: William Jones, Zollie Luther Jones, and Family, 1906-1920, 1932-1968, undated (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - Luther: William Jones, Zollie Luther Jones, and Family, 1968, undated (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Luther: Charles Voges, Riette Jones Voges, and Family, 1919, 1942-1952, undated (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - Luther: Charles Voges, Riette Jones Voges, and Family, 1952-1957, 1965, undated (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Bagby: Anne Luther Bagby, 1865, 1928, undated (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Bagby: Anne Luther Bagby, undated (Box 129 OVZ, Folder 7)
  - Bagby: William Buck Bagby, 1878, 1887-1888, 1893 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Bagby: William Buck Bagby, 1919, 1928, 1937-1939, undated (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Bagby: William Buck Bagby, undated (Box 129 OVZ, Folder 8)
  - Bagby: William Buck Bagby, Anne Luther Bagby, and Family, circa 1881-1949, undated (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Bagby: William Buck Bagby, Anne Luther Bagby, and Missionaries, undated (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - Bagby: Helen Bagby Harrison and Family, 1905-1962, undated (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Bagby: William Coleman Harrison, Helen Bagby Harrison, and Family, 1912-1942, undated (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - Bagby: William Coleman Harrison, Helen Bagby Harrison, and Family, 1941-1942, undated (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Bagby: William Coleman Harrison, Helen Bagby Harrison, and Family, 1942-1950, undated (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - Bagby: William Coleman Harrison, Helen Bagby Harrison, and Family, 1950-1962, undated (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Bagby: William Coleman Harrison, Helen Bagby Harrison, and Family, 1963-1973, undated (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Bagby: William Coleman Harrison, Helen Bagby Harrison, and Family: (1 of 3), undated (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Bagby: William Coleman Harrison, Helen Bagby Harrison, and Family: (2 of 3), undated (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Bagby: William Coleman Harrison, Helen Bagby Harrison, and Family: (3 of 3), undated (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Bagby: William Bagby Harrison, Sybil Harrison, and Family, 1950, 1962 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Bagby: Albert Ian Bagby, Thelma Frith Bagby, and Family, 1905-1956, undated (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - Bagby: Albert Ian Bagby, Thelma Frith Bagby, and Family, 1933-1965, undated (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Bagby: Albert Ian Bagby, Thelma Frith Bagby, and Family, circa 1960s, undated (Box 106, Folder 13)
  - Bagby: Alice Anne Bagby, 1896, 1921-1924, 1933, undated (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Bagby: Ermine Bagby, 1883-1903 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Bagby: Sydney Sowell, Ermine Bagby Sowell, and Family, 1907-1945, undated (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - Bagby: Sydney Sowell, Ermine Bagby Sowell, and Family, 1937-1962, undated (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - Bagby: Sydney Sowell, Ermine Bagby Sowell, and Family, 1928-1929, 1941, 1960, undated (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - Bagby: Taylor Crawford Bagby, Frances Bagby, and Family, 1901-1929, undated (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Bagby: Taylor Crawford Bagby, Frances Bagby, and Family, 1923-1950s, undated (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Bagby: Taylor Crawford Bagby, Frances Bagby, and Family, 1932-1963, undated (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - Bagby: Luther Henry Bagby, Willson Bagby, and Family, 1883-1936, undated (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - Bagby: Oliver H. Bagby, 1916, 1918-1919, undated (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - Bagby: Extended Family, circa 1850s-1970s, undated (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Bagby: Extended Family, circa 1880-1935, undated (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Bagby: Extended Family, 1890-1922, undated (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Bagby: Extended Family, 1920 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Bagby: General, circa 1910-1950 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Smith: General, 1921-1943, undated (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Smith: General, 1931-1963, undated (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Smith: General, 1935-1953, undated (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Smith: General, 1936-1960, undated (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Smith: General, 1947-1953 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Smith: General, 1964-1972, undated (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Smith: General: (1 of 2), undated (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Smith: General: (2 of 2), undated (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Smith: Saó Paulo Villa Americana, 1915-1923, undated (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - Smith: Extended Family: Cowsert and Stafford Families, 1918-1961, undated (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Smith: Extended Family, 1913, 1934 (Box 129 OVZ, Folder 9)
  - Smith: Extended Family, 1930-1943 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Smith: Extended Family, 1930-1952, undated (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Smith: Alice Bagby Smith, 1920-1944, undated (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - Smith: Alice Bagby Smith, 1918-1922, 1930, undated (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - Smith: Harley Smith, 1918-1966, undated (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Smith: Harley Smith, 1936, undated (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Smith: Helen Frances Smith, 1924-1928, 1932, 1937-1945, undated (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Smith: Jimmye Standard Hillman, Helen Frances Smith Hillman, and Family, 1941-1956, undated (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Smith: Jimmye Standard Hillman, Helen Frances Smith Hillman, and Family, 1942-1966, undated (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Smith: Jimmye Standard Hillman, Helen Frances Smith Hillman, and Family, 1944-1956 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Smith: Jimmye Standard Hillman, Helen Frances Smith Hillman, and Family, 1953-1958, undated (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Smith: Jimmye Standard Hillman, Helen Frances Smith Hillman, and Family, 1953-1967 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - Smith: Jimmye Standard Hillman, Helen Frances Smith Hillman, and Family, 1968-1970, undated (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Smith: Thelma Lou Smith, 1937-1938, 1940-1942, 1953-1954 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Smith: William F. Cooper, Thelma Lou Smith Cooper, and Family, 1953, 1959, 1962-1971, undated (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Smith: William F. Cooper, Thelma Lou Smith Cooper, and Family, 1971-1972, undated (Box 109, Folder 12)
  - Smith: William F. Cooper, Thelma Lou Smith Cooper, and Family, undated (Box 109, Folder 13)
  - Smith: Paul Bagby Smith, 1929-1930, 1935, 1940-1949 (Box 109, Folder 14)
  - Smith: Paul Bagby Smith, 1929, 1935, 1945, 1949, undated (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Smith: Paul Bagby Smith, Gloria Painter Smith, Alba Ferrer Smith, and Families, 1944-1966, undated (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Smith: Paul Bagby Smith, Gloria Painter Smith, Alba Ferrer Smith, and Families, 1945, 1950, 1959, 1966-1967, undated (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Smith: Negatives: (1 of 14), 1919-1937, undated (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Smith: Negatives: (2 of 14), 1919-1937, undated (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Smith: Negatives: (3 of 14), 1919-1937, undated (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Smith: Negatives: (4 of 14), 1919-1937, undated (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - Smith: Negatives: (5 of 14), 1919-1937, undated (Box 110, Folder 8)
  - Smith: Negatives: (6 of 14), 1919-1937, undated (Box 110, Folder 9)
  - Smith: Negatives: (7 of 14), 1919-1937, undated (Box 110, Folder 10)
  - Smith: Negatives: (8 of 14), 1919-1937, undated (Box 110, Folder 11)
  - Smith: Negatives: (9 of 14), 1919-1937, undated (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Smith: Negatives: (10 of 14), 1919-1937, undated (Box 110, Folder 13)
  - Smith: Negatives: (11 of 14), 1919-1937, undated (Box 110, Folder 14)
  - Smith: Negatives: (12 of 14), 1919-1937, undated (Box 110, Folder 15)
  - Smith: Negatives: (13 of 14), 1919-1937, undated (Box 110, Folder 16)
  - Smith: Negatives: (14 of 14), 1919-1937, undated (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - Smith: Negatives: (1 of 8), 1939, undated (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Smith: Negatives: (2 of 8), 1939, undated (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Smith: Negatives: (3 of 8), 1939, undated (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Smith: Negatives: (4 of 8), 1939, undated (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Smith: Negatives: (5 of 8), 1939, undated (Box 111, Folder 5)
  - Smith: Negatives: (6 of 8), 1939, undated (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - Smith: Negatives: (7 of 8), 1939, undated (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Smith: Negatives: (8 of 8), 1939, undated (Box 111, Folder 8)
  - Smith: Negatives, 1945, 1953, undated (Box 111, Folder 9)
  - Schools: Colegio Batista (Porto Alegre): Students, circa 1920s-1940s, undated (Box 111, Folder 10)
  - Schools: Colegio Batista (Porto Alegre): Students, 1926-1946, undated (Box 111, Folder 11)
  - Schools: Colegio Batista (Porto Alegre): Students, 1927-1935, undated (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - Schools: Colegio Batista (Porto Alegre): Students, 1927-1939, undated (Box 111, Folder 13)
  - Schools: Colegio Batista (Porto Alegre): Students, 1928-1961, undated (Box 111, Folder 14)
  - Schools: Colegio Batista (Porto Alegre): Students, 1935-1940s, undated (Box 111, Folder 15)
  - Schools: Colegio Batista (Porto Alegre): Students, 1939-1942, undated (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - Schools: Colegio Batista (Porto Alegre): Students, 1940-1943, undated (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Schools: Colegio Batista (Porto Alegre): Students, 1940-1945, undated (Box 112, Folder 2)
  - Schools: Colegio Batista (Porto Alegre): Students, circa 1940s-1960s, undated (Box 112, Folder 3)
  - Schools: Colegio Batista (Porto Alegre): Students, 1943-1945, undated (Box 112, Folder 4)
  - Schools: Colegio Batista (Porto Alegre): Students, 1943-1950s (Box 112, Folder 5)
  - Schools: Colegio Batista (Porto Alegre): Students, 1944-1953, undated (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Schools: Colegio Batista (Porto Alegre): Students, circa 1950s, undated (Box 112, Folder 7)
  - Schools: Colegio Batista (Porto Alegre): Students, 1955-1963, undated (Box 112, Folder 8)
  - Schools: Colegio Batista (Porto Alegre): Fortieth Anniversary, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Schools: Colegio Batista: (São Paulo): (1 of 2), 1900s-1920s, undated (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Schools: Colegio Batista: (São Paulo): (2 of 2), 1900s-1920s, undated (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Schools: Colegio Batista: (São Paulo), 1916-1921, undated (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Schools: Colegio Progresso Brasileiro: (São Paulo), undated (Box 129 OVZ, Folder 10)
  - Schools: Baylor Female College [University of Mary Hardin-Baylor], 1889 (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Schools: Baylor Female College [University of Mary Hardin-Baylor], 1915-1918 (Box 112, Folder 14)
  - Schools: Baylor Female College [University of Mary Hardin-Baylor], 1918-1919 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Schools: Baylor Female College [University of Mary Hardin-Baylor], undated (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Schools: Mary Hardin-Baylor College [University of Mary Hardin-Baylor], 1943 (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: Churches: Igreja Batista Central, 1937-1960, undated (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: Churches: Igreja Batista Central, 1965-1972, undated (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: Churches: Igreja Batista Central, 1968 (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: Churches: General, 1920s-1960s, undated (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: Churches: General, 1928-1965 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: Churches: General, 1932-1961, undated (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: Churches: General, 1949-1960s (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: Churches: General, 1955-1961, undated (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: Churches: General, 1957, 1964, undated (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: Churches: General, 1963-1969 (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: Classes and Activities, 1935-1962, undated (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: Classes and Activities, 1945-1962, undated (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: General, 1920-1930, undated (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: General, 1921-1931, undated (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: General, 1927-1942, undated (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: General, 1942, undated (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: General, 1946-1962, undated (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: General, 1967 (Box 129 OVZ, Folder 11)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: General, 1920s, undated (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Churches, Organizations, and Associations: General, undated (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Friends and Associates: General, circa 1880s-1910 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1908, 1920-1936, undated (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1912-1944 (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1919-1956, undated (Box 114, Folder 14)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1920-1928 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1920-1931 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1920-1944 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1920-1962, undated (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Friends and Associates: General, circa 1920-1970 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1921-1959, undated (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1924, 1961, undated (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Friends and Associates: General, circa 1924-1970, undated (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1924, undated (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1928-1941, undated (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1931-1932, 1946, 1952, 1968, 1970, undated (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1931-1936 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1936-1965 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1937-1941 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1937-1949, undated (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1941-1960 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1944-1964, undated (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1950-1968, undated (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1950-1968, undated (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1951-1963 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1955-1956, 1961 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1960-1972, undated (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1966-1972, undated (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Friends and Associates: General, 1971-1972, undated (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Friends and Associates: General, undated (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Friends and Associates: Group Pictures, 1892 (Box 129 OVZ, Folder 12)
  - Friends and Associates: Group Pictures, 1921-1945 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Friends and Associates: Group Pictures, 1922-1931 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Friends and Associates: Group Pictures, 1928, 1937-1939 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Friends and Associates: Group Pictures, 1936-1969, undated (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Friends and Associates: Group Pictures, 1939-1961 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Friends and Associates: Group Pictures, 1945-1969 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Friends and Associates: Group Pictures, 1961-1965 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Friends and Associates: Group Pictures, 1965-1974, undated (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Friends and Associates: Group Pictures, 1969-1972, undated (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Friends and Associates: Group Pictures: (1 of 3), undated (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Friends and Associates: Group Pictures: (2 of 3), undated (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Friends and Associates: Group Pictures: (3 of 3), undated (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Travels: United States of America, 1921-1944, undated (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Travels: Rio Grande do Sul, 1921, undated (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Travels: Rio Grande do Sul, 1921-1969, undated (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Travels: Panama, 1921-1936, undated (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Travels: São Paulo, 1920s, uncated (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Travels: Scenes from Brazil, undated (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Travels: Buildings around the World, circa 1920-1971 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Travels: Photo Album of Scenes in Temple, Texas, 1889-1917 (Box 129 OVZ, Folder 13)
  - Travels: Baker's House, Houston, Texas, undated (Box 129 OVZ, Folder 14)
  - General: (1 of 4), circa 1920s-1940s, undated (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - General: (2 of 4), circa 1920s-1940s, undated (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - General: (3 of 4), circa 1920s-1940s, undated (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - General: (4 of 4), circa 1920s-1940s, undated (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - General, undated (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - First Baptist Congress, Bahia, Brazil (Alice Alyne Goolsby, William Buck Bagby), 1907 June 20 (Box 129 OVZ, Folder 15)
- Scrapbooks, 1877-1971; 6; 5 document boxes and three boxes of oversized materials.
  The scrapbooks in this series include personal scrapbooks that were assembled by family members as well as subject file scrapbooks and topical scrapbooks. The series includes four document boxes and three oversized boxes.
  - General: Subject File Scrapbook: (1 of 7), 1941-1957 (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - General: Subject File Scrapbook: (2 of 7), 1941-1957 (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - General: Subject File Scrapbook: (3 of 7), 1941-1957 (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - General: Subject File Scrapbook: (4 of 7), 1941-1957 (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - General: Subject File Scrapbook: (5 of 7), 1941-1957 (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - General: Subject File Scrapbook: (6 of 7), 1941-1957 (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - General: Subject File Scrapbook: (7 of 7), 1941-1957 (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - General: Subject File Scrapbook: (1 of 9), 1941-1962 (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - General: Subject File Scrapbook: (2 of 9), 1941-1962 (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - General: Subject File Scrapbook: (3 of 9), 1941-1962 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - General: Subject File Scrapbook: (4 of 9), 1941-1962 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - General: Subject File Scrapbook: (5 of 9), 1941-1962 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - General: Subject File Scrapbook: (6 of 9), 1941-1962 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - General: Subject File Scrapbook: (7 of 9), 1941-1962 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - General: Subject File Scrapbook: (8 of 9), 1941-1962 (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - General: Subject File Scrapbook: (9 of 9), 1941-1962 (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - General: Scrapbook 1: (1 of 3), undated (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - General: Scrapbook 1: (2 of 3), undated (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - General: Scrapbook 1: (3 of 3), undated (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - General: Scrapbook 2: (1 of 2), 1877-1949 (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - General: Scrapbook 2: (2 of 2), 1877-1949 (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - General: Scrapbook 3: (1 of 2), 1969 (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - General: Scrapbook 3: (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - General: Scrapbook 4: (1 of 3), 1937, undated (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - General: Scrapbook 4: (2 of 3), 1937, undated (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - General: Scrapbook 4: (3 of 3), 1937, undated (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - John Hill Luther: (1 of 8), 1898 (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - John Hill Luther: (2 of 8), 1898 (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - John Hill Luther: (3 of 8), 1898 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - John Hill Luther: (4 of 8), 1898 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - John Hill Luther: (5 of 8), 1898 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - John Hill Luther: (6 of 8), 1898 (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - John Hill Luther: (7 of 8), 1898 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - John Hill Luther: (8 of 8), 1898 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - John Hill Luther Scrapbook 1: (1 of 4), undated (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - John Hill Luther Scrapbook 1: (2 of 4), undated (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - John Hill Luther Scrapbook 1: (3 of 4), undated (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - John Hill Luther Scrapbook 1: (4 of 4), undated (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - John Hill Luther Scrapbook 2: (1 of 4), undated (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - John Hill Luther Scrapbook 2: (2 of 4), undated (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - John Hill Luther Scrapbook 2: (3 of 4), undated (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - John Hill Luther Scrapbook 2: (4 of 4), undated (Box 124 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Alice Bagby: Baylor University: Loose Materials: Inside Front Cover, 1917-1919, undated (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Alice Bagby: Baylor University: Loose Materials: Inside Back Cover, 1917-1919, undated (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Alice Bagby Smith: Subject File Scrapbook: (1 of 5), 1932-1953 (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Alice Bagby Smith: Subject File Scrapbook: (2 of 5), 1932-1953 (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - Alice Bagby Smith: Subject File Scrapbook: (3 of 5), 1932-1953 (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - Alice Bagby Smith: Subject File Scrapbook: (4 of 5), 1932-1953 (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - Alice Bagby Smith: Subject File Scrapbook: (5 of 5), 1932-1953 (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - Alice Bagby Smith: (1 of 3), 1933-1941 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Alice Bagby Smith: (2 of 3), 1933-1941 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Alice Bagby Smith: (3 of 3), 1933-1941 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Alice Bagby Smith: Loose Materials: Inside Back Cover: (1 of 3), 1934-1957 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Alice Bagby Smith: Loose Materials: Inside Back Cover: (2 of 3), 1934-1957 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Alice Bagby Smith: Loose Materials: Inside Back Cover: (3 of 3), 1934-1957 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Alice Bagby Smith: Loose Materials: Pages 1-15, 1934-1957 (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Alice Bagby Smith: Loose Materials: Pages 16-20, 1934-1957 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Alice Bagby Smith, 1934-1957 (Box 124 OVZ, Folder 3)
  - Alice Bagby Smith: (1 of 3), 1948 (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Alice Bagby Smith: (2 of 3), 1948 (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Alice Bagby Smith: (3 of 3), 1948 (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Alice Bagby Smith: Baylor University, undated (Box 123 OVZ, Folder 1)
  - Nellie Buck: (1 of 3), circa 1954-1963 (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Nellie Buck: (2 of 3), circa 1954-1963 (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Nellie Buck: (3 of 3), circa 1954-1963 (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Portuguese Hymns, 1959 (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - Religious, Club Meeting Notes, 1934-1942 (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - Helen Frances Smith, 1924-1925 (Box 121, Folder 17)
  - John Hill Luther Sermons and Sketches, undated (Box 121, Folder 18)
  - John Hill Luther Sermons and Sketches Loose Materials, undated (Box 121, Folder 19)
  - Portuguese Religious Tracts, 1949-circa 1961 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Religious Notes, 1918-1921 (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Clippings and Notes, 1951-1953 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Friends, 1971 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Jones Voges Photographs, circa 1940 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Colégio Batista, Porto Alegre, Brazil Dedication Photographs, 1968 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - English Speaking Club Subject Files and Photographs: (1 of 4), 1949-1955 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - English Speaking Club Subject Files and Photographs: (2 of 4), 1949-1955 (Box 122, Folder 8)